History's biggest disaster comes to an end.
The Last Sharknado: It's About Time is a action, comedy,
horror film directed by Anthony C. Ferrante.
Our hero Fin has battled sharks all over the globe, but in this last
installment he will tackle the final shark-tier - time travel.
Fin Shepard, played by Ian Ziering.
April Shepard, played by Tara Reid.
Nova Clarke, played by Cassie Scerbo.
Skye, played by Vivica A. Fox.
Bryan, played by Judah Friedlander.
New Bryan, played by Debra Wilson.
The Last Sharknado: It's About Time is a 2018 American made-for-television science fiction
comedy disaster film and the sixth installment in the Sharknado film series.
The film was directed by Anthony C.
Ferrante with Ian Ziering, Tara Reid and Cassie Scerbo
reprising their roles from the previous installments.
In the film, Fin and his gang use time travel in order to
prevent sharknadoes from ever happening.
A prequel is in development.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and thought_provoking.